thelinkjuicer.com 2011-12-31

# The Link Juicer - Privacy Statement

The Link Juicer takes the protection of your online privacy very seriously. Please read the following to understand The Link Juicer's privacy practices. The Link Juicer may need to change its privacy statement from time to time, because of changes in its business, or in its attempts to serve your needs better. The Link Juicer will use reasonable efforts to publish any changes to its privacy statement. 

###  What information does The Link Juicer gather? 

The Link Juicer may need to gather specific information from you at times such as your name and email address, among other personal information. Information that is essential for The Link Juicer to provide the services and/or products that are requested by you is generally designated as "Required". Additional information that would allow The Link Juicer flexibility in providing its services or products, and may be used for internal statistical studies or market research, is generally indicated as "Optional". For example, an email address is required when subscribing to an online service, whereas a fax number may not be essential, but would provide another means of communication between you and The Link Juicer. Just how much personally identifiable information you disclose to The Link Juicer is completely at your discretion. 

###  How does The Link Juicer use personal information? 

When you give The Link Juicer information about yourself, you understand that you are agreeing to allow The Link Juicer access to, storage of, and use of, the data in any of the countries where The Link Juicer does business. The Link Juicer may use the information you submit for any purposes related to The Link Juicer's business, including, but not limited to, generating statistical studies, conducting market research, improving its products and services, sending you surveys, and notifying you of product upgrades and updates, new products, special offers, seminars and conventions and any other changes within The Link Juicer that may affect you. 

###  What choices do you have about how your personal information is used and what is The Link Juicer's commitment to data quality and reliability? 

The Link Juicer respects your privacy and realises that not everyone likes to receive promotional emails. Should you communicate with The Link Juicer via one of the email address that may be made available to The Link Juicer users, this email address will only be used to communicate with you regarding the issue at hand. It will not be used to send you emails unrelated to the issue unless you request such emails. 

###  Does The Link Juicer share the information that it gathers with third parties? 

The Link Juicer uses your personal information internally and does not share it with any third parties. In the event that you opt in to a mailing list that explicitly includes offers from The Link Juicer' partners, offers will be sent to you directly from The Link Juicer' servers. Your personal details will not be disclosed to the partners unless you make contact with them yourself. 

###  Does The Link Juicer share the information that it gathers with government agencies or law enforcement? 

The Link Juicer reserves the right to monitor, and disclose to, government officials or law enforcement, without your consent, any communications and personally identifiable information, whenever prompted to do so, by legal authorities, even when you have requested that your information not be disclosed to third parties. 

###  What is The Link Juicer's commitment to data security? 

The Link Juicer recognises your concern for security, and will use reasonable efforts to establish secure connections with you and to limit access to databases containing personal information to authorised personnel only. 

###  Does The Link Juicer use cookies? 

"Cookies" give users a unique, random ID by storing small text files onto a user's computer hard drive with the user's browser. Cookies enable a web site to recognize sequential page views as belonging to the same user. The Link Juicer may use cookies on its web site now and in the future. The Link Juicer's cookies do not and will not contain personally identifying information. Users are free to modify their web browser settings to prevent the acceptance of cookies. 

###  Does The Link Juicer store IP addresses? 

IP addresses are automatically logged by web server software. These logs are used for traffic analysis, and stored for a short period of time. 

###  What are The Link Juicer's contact procedures? 

If you believe The Link Juicer has not adhered to its privacy statement, you may notify The Link Juicer [here](mailto:privacy@thelinkjuicer.com). The Link Juicer will use reasonable efforts to promptly resolve any issues.
